http://www.cinequest.org/terms-privacy

Contact Us
E-mail: contact@cinequest.org for general questions, customerservice@cinequest.org for support related inquiries.
Phone: (408) 295-3378 (FEST)
Fax: (408) 995-5713
Mailing Address: Cinequest P.O. Box 720040 San Jose CA 95172-0040
Cinequest Updates
Join our email notification list and get the biggest news delivered right to your in-box. Stay in the loop with Cinequest as we announce our film line-up, maverick stars and festival happenings. Please click here to sign up on our home page. You can also stay ahead of the curve by becoming a fan of Cinequest on Facebook, or by following us on Twitter
Terms and Conditions
SCOPE
This Privacy Policy covers Cinequest's online and offline treatment of personally identifiable information that is collected when you are on the Cinequest web site ("Site"). If you choose to visit sites of other parties by clicking on the links we provide, this policy does not cover the treatment of personally identifiable information that may be collected by those web sites ("Third-Party Sites").
DATA SECURITY
The Cinequest Site has security measures in place to protect the information under our control. We use secure socket layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of commerce transactions. We encrypt your personal and financial information as it travels over the Internet. We do not store any credit card information for the protection of our consumers. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
Cinequest collects personally identifiable information including name, address, email address, phone number, ticket type, and event information when you register for an account or purchase products or services. Cinequest also collects information from your browser including browser type, browser version, browser settings, operating system, pages visited, your IP Address, and Cookies. Cinequest uses the above collected information for general purposes such as allowing you to add products and services to your shopping cart, tailoring the content within the Site to match your interests, and ensuring that the site continues to operate properly with commonly used
operating systems and browsers.
Cinequest also uses this information to send you information, offers and other promotional materials from Cinequest and selected third parties. You may opt out of receiving information directly from Cinequest by contacting us here: customerservice@cinequest.org.
Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of processing or refunding the transactions which take place on Cinequest systems. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity that uses financial information, you consent to our providing your financial information to third parties including the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process the transaction. We may also we may share your financial information with applicable Contracted Clients (venues/promoters/team owners/organizations that contract directly with Cinequest for ticketing services), primarily for facilitating "will call" ticket pick up, dispute resolution, refunds, and customer service at the event venue on the date of the event.
Children under the age of 13 are prohibited from submitting personal information to Cinequest. Federal Law prohibits web sites from collecting and/or distributing personal information from children without parental consent. At this time, Cinequest has no effective means to obtain and track parental consent. Therefore, Cinequest must prohibit the submission of personal information from children under the age of 13.
INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE
The act of purchasing a ticket or completing a registration form, automatically grants Cinequest the right to share your personal information with our Contracted Clients (venues/promoters/team owners/organizations that contract directly with Cinequest for ticketing services) in association with event(s) you are purchasing a ticket for. The opportunity to opt-out, or not to consent to our sharing of your personal information with them is not available at this time. Contracted Clients may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies, and may consequently use your personal information to contact
you and may share your personal information with others. You will need to contact those Contracted Clients to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. You may contact Cinequest to request the Contracted Client's contact information.
Cinequest does not share, sell or rent any of your information with parties other than Contracted Clients. If Cinequest changes this policy in the future, changes will be posted in the area of the web site on the date they become effective and any information used or collected after that date will be subject to the policy in effect at that time. We recommend that you review this policy each time you purchase a ticket to ensure your knowledge of the current policy.
COOKIES
Cookies are small text files that are downloaded to your computer. Cookies cannot damage your computer. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to identify you. Unless you've chosen to submit personal information to Cinequest though registration or the purchase of products and/or services, Cinequest cannot identify you. Cookies are used by Cinequest to allow the smooth operation of the Site and to track your activity so that we may tailor the content of the Site to match your interests
REFUND POLICY
Other than for an event being cancelled, ALL SALES ARE FINAL, NO REFUNDS, NO EXCHANGES. If an event is cancelled or rescheduled, or we cannot seat you, Cinequest will exchange that ticket for another event of equal or greater value at the Cinequest Box Office.
SUPPORT CINEQUEST
Your support empowers our team >
STORY OF CINEQUEST
Bridging Silicon Valley’s technologies and spirit of innovation with the arts to empower great creations. Watch now >
MAVERICK VOICES
Watch Maverick Spirit Award-Winners from Cinequest Film & Creativity Festival speak on creativity, innovation, and empowerment. Watch Now >
